bsprewards.com 2003-12-02

# BSP Rewards Privacy Policy

**_Privacy Policy_**

BSP Rewards firmly believes that personal privacy should be protected. We are acutely aware that evolving technologies present new challenges for user privacy. We work to comply with the guidelines set by numerous privacy organizations to ensure that we stay on the cutting edge of privacy protection. 

**By visiting BSP Rewards, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice. **

BSP Rewards is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. BSP Rewards collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

 **Registration**  
In order to use this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. It is optional for the user to provide demographic information (such as income level and gender), and unique identifiers (such as social security number), but encouraged so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site. 

**Order**  
We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user.  
 **  
What Personal Information About Customers Does BSP Rewards Gather?**  
The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your experience at BSP Rewards. Here are the types of information we gather. 

**Information You Give Us**  
We receive and store any information you enter when you register for our reward program or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our offers, and communicating with you. 

**What about Cookies?**  
We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses BSP Rewards. The Federal Trade Commission provides useful information about online privacy on its own Web site, Site Seeing on the Internet. 

**E-mail Communications**  
To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from BSP Rewards if your computer supports such capabilities. We also compare our customer list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our customers. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your preferences by visiting the Profile section on our site.

 **Information from Other Sources**  
For reasons such as improving personalization of our service (for example, providing better product recommendations or special offers that we think will interest you), we might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. 

**Does BSP Rewards Share the Information It Receives?**  
Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We share customer information only with the subsidiaries BSP Rewards, and as described below. 

**Surveys & Contests**

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

 **Tell-A-Friend**

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. BSP Rewards will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. BSP Rewards stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. The friend may contact BSP Rewards at remove@bsprewards.com to request the removal of this information from their database.  

 **Links**  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, BSP Rewards, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

 **Security**

This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line.

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'.

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage.

 **Supplementation of Information**

In order for this website to enhance its ability to tailor the site to an individual's preference, we combine information about the purchasing habits of users with similar information from our partners to create a personalized user profile. When a user makes a purchase from any of these companies, the companies collect and share that purchase information with us so we can tailor the site to our users' preferences.  

 **Agents**  
We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. 

**Promotional Offers**  
Sometimes we send offers to selected groups of BSP Rewards customers on behalf of other businesses. When we do this, we do not give that business your name and address. If you do not want to receive such offers, please adjust your please adjust your preferences by visiting the Profile section on our site. 

**Business Transfers**  
As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores or assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the unlikely event that BSP Rewards or substantially all of its assets are acquired; customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.

 **Protection of BSP Rewards and Others**  
We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of BSP Rewards, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

 **Special Offers  
**

We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our choice and opt-out below.

 **Site and Service Updates  
**We also send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to unsubscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email or phone.

**Correction/Updating Personal Information:  
** If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can usually be done at the member information page or by emailing our Customer Support representatives.

 **Choice/Opt-out  
** Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. For example, our order form has an 'opt-out' mechanism so users who buy a product from us, but don't want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists. 

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email or email us at remove@bsprewards.com 

Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party, or not.

 **Notification of Changes  
** If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

**Third-party Submissions**  
BSP Rewards does not accept third-party submissions, nor will the Company use any means of indirect collection that identifies our members. BSP Rewards will not share, sell, or exchange any of our members' personal information to a third party (including the affiliate website that you may have reached this service from) unless you specifically request that we do so by contacting us at info@bsprewards.com. BSP Rewards may from time to time share or publicly announce compiled, aggregated data containing no personally identifiable information. BSP Rewards will not release any information about you individually without prior consent.   
Websites that you may link to BSP Rewards or sites that link you to BSP Rewards may collect personally identifiable information about you. BSP Rewards is not responsible for other websites' privacy and security practices. Our privacy policy addresses only personal information that you provide directly to BSP Rewards. If you have questions about the privacy and security practices of the website that you reached this service from, or any other website, we encourage you to review those websites' privacy statements or contact them directly.   
Online account data including your account balance and transaction information that is gathered by BSP Rewards on your behalf is for your benefit only and will not be shared or released to a third party. It is provided to you only under the BSP Rewards User Acceptance Agreement. This privacy statement and the conditions and policies outlined herein do not imply any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any other party. If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of BSP Rewards, or your dealings with this website, you can contact BSP Rewards by calling during normal business hours (561) 392-4550 or by sending and email to info@bpsrewards.com  

**Logfiles**  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

 **Special Note For Children**  
While BSP Rewards is concerned about the protection of children's privacy; we do not consider our web site or service to be aimed at children. Accordingly, children who are 16 years of age or younger, may **NOT** apply for membership at BSP Rewards and are not eligible for our service. Furthermore, anyone under 18 will not be able to participate in our shopping club. BSP Rewards does not sell products for purchase by children. We sell children's products for purchase by adults. If you are under 18, you may use BSP Rewards only with involvement of a parent or guardian. 

**On our registered credit card program:**

* We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.

* We reveal only the last five digits of your credit card numbers when confirming your membership enrollment. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.

* It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

 **On our toolbar:**

No one including our advertisers will be able to identify you individually. All data is treated in groups for our data processing purposes, and at no stage will the advertiser know who you are. Data shared with advertisers is in anonymous group statistical form. This allows advertisers to participate more effectively by sending out ads targeted to various member groups based on their interests. For example: an advertiser may be told that 10,000 members are interested in receiving ads related to golf. But, at no stage will they "know" who these 10,000 members actually are. The program is designed to make it **impossible** for outside companies to access personal information.

 **Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions**  
If you choose to visit BSP Rewards, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Florida. If you have any concern about privacy at BSP Rewards, please send us a thorough description to [privacy@bsprewards.com](mailto:privacy@bsprewards.com), and we will try to resolve it. Our business changes constantly. This Notice and the Conditions of Use will change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Notice in effect at the time of use. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. 

We will honor a request by you to terminate your account. Upon termination of an account, information about you will be erased.

If you have any questions please contact us at: [privacy@bsprewards.com](mailto:privacy@bsprewards.com)

Sincerely, 

BSP Rewards Privacy Department   
  
1515 N. Federal Hwy. Suite 300  
Boca Raton, FL 33432-1994  
Phone: (561) 392-4550   Fax: (561) 864-1065
